wwfoldschool.com 2019-10-17

# Privacy Policy & GDPR Compliance | WWF Old School

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which **  Dynamite Digital Media ** collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the WWFOldSchool.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Dynamite Digital Media.

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, subscribe to the newsletter, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**How we use collected information**

Dynamite Digital Media may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:  
– To improve customer service: Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.  
– To personalize user experience: We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.  
– To improve our Site: We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.  
– To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature: To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.  
– To send periodic emails: We may use your email address ( _only if you have subscribed to our newsletters_ ) to send latest articles/news and other updates on the site. It may also be used to respond to visitor inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.  
– To serve ads: We serve you tailored ads on our website. We offer you choices regarding personalized ads, but you cannot opt-out of seeing other ads.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Our Site is in compliance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for Users.

**Sharing your personal information**

We **DO NOT** sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

We do not share your personal data with any third-party advertisers or ad networks for their advertising except for: (i) hashed or device identifiers (to the extent they are personal data in some countries); (ii) with your separate permission or (iii) data already visible to any users of the website (e.g. profile). However, if you view or click on an ad on or off our site or apps, the ad provider will get a signal that someone visited the page that displayed the ad, and they may through the use of mechanisms such as cookies determine it is you. Advertising partners can associate personal data collected by the advertiser directly from you with our cookies and similar technologies. In such instances, we seek to contractually require such advertising partners to obtain your explicit, opt-in consent before doing so.

**Compliance with children’s online privacy protection act**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

Dynamite Digital Media has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us by filling up a form [here](https://wwfoldschool.com/contact-us/).

This document was last updated on **May 26, 2018.**
